Joyboy...
...has returned!
What happened...
...to me?
How come I can still stand up?
I might've lost...
...but now it's gettin' fun!
Joyboy?!
Does he mean Luffy?!
Is that what Zunesha said?!
You've come to...
Gentleman Pirate!
lond
Luffy?!
Eh?
Is that the Straw Hat Man?
Straw Hat?!
Hey!
He's still kickin', yessir!
Luffy's not dead?!
Big Bro's still alive?!
Thank goodness!
Sacrificing one of our best agents...
Suppose there was some possible future where
we would beg for this outcome?
Eliminating dangerous variables
is always best.
Since its inception,
the World Government has sought after
the Gum-Gum Fruit...
And yet, not once has it come
into our possession...
Not even once,
in eight hundred years!
It is as if...
...the Devil Fruit evades us, no?
Not entirely implausible.
Zoan-type Devil Fruits
have wills of their own.
Furthermore, that Devil Fruit
bears the name of a god.
The Gum-Gum Fruit
goes by another name...
The Zoan-type, Human-Human Fruit,
Mythical Type, Model:
Nika.
They say his body takes on
the very properties of rubber itself.
He fights as he fancies,
and brings smiles to
the faces of the people.
The Warrior of Liberation...
Also known as...
Nika, the Sun God!
Awakening the power is said to bestow upon
the user's body even greater physical strength...
...and freedom.
It is said that in all the world,
there is no power more...
co.ridiculous.
Komurasaki!
Hi-Hiyori!
Y-Y-You know,
I really did like Oden, after all!
Think about it, won't you?!
I was exploited by Kaido!
Let's run away from this,
you and I!
Just remove this nail from me...
Pray tell who would lend
you their ear now!
My father...
...kept his word to you,
did he not?
He believed that you and Kaido...
...would set free the Land of Wano,
and so he spent five years...
...making a complete fool of himself!
And not once did he
complain of it to his family!
My father kept his word!
He took you at your word:
you would set his people free...
And so he withstood
an hour of torture by boiling!
His body, cooked alive
by the scorching oil!
Forever and ever,
always bearing a smile upon his face...
Alas, the nation whole
was taken hostage,
and he alone its burden bore...
O, Father, how you suffered so!
How hellish it must have been!
What is the matter, Hiyori?
Father, are you fine with
people speaking ill of you?
Aye, 'tis just as well.
Why?
Because I have all of you!
Really?
Then, I'll always be with you!
Weeell... Oden was a
most impressive samurai!
Deserving of praise, even!
As Shogun, I would be pleased
to reward your father!
My name is...
...Kozuki Hiyori!
You will hold your tongue,
insolent knave!
Even as I starved and
wore little more than tatters...
I strove to live up
to my father's name!
There was never a single day
when you were the true Shogun!
You are as foolish
as you are uncouth!
And the more you act as such,
the more lives will have been shattered in vain!
N-Now, now! No closer!
Don't do anything rash!
Vengeance-seeking is
quite antiquated, you know!
Even if you kill me,
you can't defeat Kaido!
Orochi-sama...
I have failed...
You!
Is that you, Kanjuro?!
This is... as far as I go.
You're just in time!
I grant you a new stage!
Turn that woman to ash!
Charge!
The failure of a woman
that endured hardship for twenty years!
What a tragicomedy!
Do you see?!
Vestige of the Kozuki, Hiyori!
This... This is the luck...
of the strong!
Orochi-sama...
Not toward me!
Don't come toward me!
Kanjuro, you damned fool!
Hiyori!
Save me!
Oww hothothot owhotow!
The Dawn... will surely come.
Our clan, the Kozuki...
...always keeps their word!
I can do everything
I've ever wanted!
And I think I can get
a little more fightin' in!
Man, my heartbeat sounds funny!
I've hit my peak!
This is it!
Gear 5!
Hey, what's wrong?!
Someone's Color of the Conqueror?!
Where's it coming from?!
Hey, the bunch of ya!
What's that on the roof?
Huuuh?!
Kaido-san?!
Straw Hat?!
Is that Luffy?!
Musclin', musclin'!
Muscles!
Upsy-daisy!
Straw Hat...!
So you're alive, huh!
Gotta thank you!
Heh?
Huh?!
Hwuuuuh?!
Blast Breath!
Get 'im!
I feel bad about what
that moron did earlier...
I didn't want to win like that.
Dun worry 'bout it.
Let's settle this!
I thought for sure you were dead.
Me too!
Seeing as how the rubber power's
affecting other things...
It's probably safe to say
your Paramythia's awakened, yeah?
But something
about it's a little off...
That kind of
full-body transformation...
...is something you
only see with Zoans!
So dark! So cramped!
Ya big jerk!
Muscly muscles...
...power!
Ya-hoo!
I'm a shootin' star!
Just call me Shooting Luffytaro!
Enjoy, go!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Stahgp mehssgin'
'roundg ing ere...!
Eh?!
Huuuuh?!
What is that?!
What is going on?!
Haven't the slightest!
Kaido became quite rotund!
Did he have a form like that?
Dammit, what's going on with me?!
My body ain't made of rubber!
This's a riot!
There's a couple of lights!
The fun's just gettin' started!
Gum-Gum...
...Escape Rocket!
Luffy?!
Gum-Gum...
...Gigant!
Whaaaa
Whaaaa?!
Whuh?!
Who is that?!
Why do I hear Luffy's voice
from up there?!
Hueh?!
Is that Luffy?!
Knock it off!
Gum-Gum...
...Jump Rope!
Blast Breath!
Eeeyowww!
Now ya've done it!
Straw Hat!
Gum-Gum...
Conqueror of Three Worlds:
...Ragnaraku!
That hoifits!
Ohmygaaaahhh!
Whaaaaaaaaaa?!
Why the hell does
Straw Hat look like that?!
Like something
right out of a comic strip...
Ooh, yow...
Very entertaining show you put on.
But, you've hit the wall, ain't ya?
Ain't ya?
You don't got what it takes
to knock me out!
Shuddup!
Who says I've hit the wall?!
I'm pooped.
Who the hell're you?!
Oh, yeah...
I was dyin' 'fore this...
Man, this really
eats up my energy...
Rest assured, you'll die knowing...
...that someone'll pass down the story
of how the bunch of you fought.
I dun...
...need...
....any of that!
Once we die,
all that's left of us is bones!
He truly is Luffy!
He did not appear to be himself,
owing to his hair and clothes turning white...
However,
his voice is fading away!
This can't end...
V
It can't end just yet, right?
Momo!
Mm!
Tama!
Kin'emon!
Pedro!
Careful,
or you're gonna die.
Ya actually ink
I'm afraid o' that?!
C'mon heart, hit that beat!
Have it your way, then!
Oh yeah, that's the sound!
Look out, Luffy!
Huuuuh!!
Yowwieee!
Just what could it all mean?!
Turning white all over,
coating himself in both
Armament and Conqueror Haki,
affecting things other than himself with his powers,
and fighting so fast and loose...
I've never seen anything like this!
Right this way!
C'mon, follow me!
Hey, that's a pretty neat attack!
Gum-Gum Rightbackatcha!
Playing games with kids is seriously...
a pain in the ass!
Three!
Two!
One!
Zero!
This's fun, don'cha think,
Kaido?!
This's pretty powerful, too!
And I get a kick outta it!
I can't make up my mind...
What do I call this attack?
"Gum-Gum" what?
Gum-GumGum-Gum...
Who the hell are you?
Huh?
I'm me!
How long has it been...!
This rhythm!
Joyboy!
Say, Joyboy...
It is as if you are actually here!
How my heart dances!
I sense this must be fate!
I cannot help but place my faith in him!
Who am I, you ask?
Monkey D. Luffy!
The man that's gonna best ya...
...and become the Pirate King!
CONTINULD
"Time's up'
Someone said again, with a laugh
Fine then, hide-and-seek playtime...
...is over
Let's go, come on (We can see it soon)
Let your heart beat out
and things will change (We can see it soon)
Grow strong, you have time
Lift up that dream
The overflowing loneliness can't sustain me alone
We were so free in our younger days
What a dumb dream
...to live
Shining a light on uncharted ways
Get on our feet and try
Let's see the ends of the world together
Together, we can go and fly